Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Video, 1955-2008; undated; 5
  - Hill & Knowlton--Management succession Bob Dilenschneider tape to H&K employees, 1986 (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-123)
  - Hill & Knowlton--Professional Development Seminar "Public Relations in the Marketing Mix", 1988 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-124)
  - Hong Kong--2nd quarter submission, 2000 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-125)
  - Hong Kong--Asia Pacific 1st quarter show reel (NTSC), 1999 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-126)
  - Hong Kong--TVC with English subtitles, 2000 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-127)
  - International reel, 1989 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-128)
  - IBM competitive reel, 1987 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-129)
  - International reel (NTSC), 1997 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-130)
  - International reel (NTSC), 1997 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-131)
  - International spots, 1995 (Box U15, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-132)
  - International spots (non JWT), Undated (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-133)
  - Jaguar XK8 Total Branding UK/Europe, 1997 (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-134)
  - James Webb Young (color), Undated (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-135)
  - JWT Christmas Party, 1983 (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-136)
  - Japan--Kellogg's Corn Flakes historical reel, Undated (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-137)
  - Japan--Kellogg's Corn Frosties historical reel, Undated (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-138)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1992 (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-139)
  - JWT Ford 80 spots (produced by Grey Advertising), 1975 (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-140)
  - JWT management transition, 1974 (Box U16, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-141)
  - JWT: Where It Comes From, Where It Is Today, and Where It Appears to be Going; Denis Lanigan Professional Development Group, 1983 (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-142)
  - JWT Tape Library--Stephen King "Market Modeling", 1984 (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-143)
  - JWTwo--Bill Ludwig, Undated (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-144)
  - JWTwo--David Moore, Undated (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-145)
  - JWTwo--Gary Topolewski, Undated (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-146)
  - JWTwo--History of JWT, Undated (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-147)
  - JWTwo--John DeCerchio, Undated (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-148)
  - JWTwo--Kevin Moehlenkamp, Undated (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-149)
  - JWTwo--Kevin Moehlenkamp, Undated (Box U17, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-150)
  - Kellogg's Cracky Total Branding example, Undated (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-151)
  - Kellogg Nutrigrain historical reel, Undated (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-152)
  - Kraft Canada--Nabob Coffee, 1998 (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-153)
  - Kraft--Phily and Ritz "Game Day", 2006 (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-154)
  - KJS Kronung "Heritage" on air (NTSC), 1997 (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-155)
  - Kraft--Phily and Ritz "Game Day", 2006 (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-156)
  - Kraft--Philly Cream Cheese (Thomas, Winter, Cooke) reel 1, 2006 (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-157)
  - Kraft--Philly Cream Cheese (Thomas, Winter, Cooke) reel 2, 2006 (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-158)
  - Larry and Allen's Best Picks Creative Standards, 1998 (Box U18, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-159)
  - Latin America--1st trimester advertising, 1995 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-160)
  - Latin America--Best of 1997-1998 tape 1 of 3 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-161)
  - Latin America--Best of 1997-1998 tape 2 of 3 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-162)
  - Latin America--Best of 1997-1998 tape 3 of 3 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-163)
  - Latin America--Patricio Bonta compilation (NTSC), 2000 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-164)
  - Latin America reel, 2000 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-165)
  - "Live on Prodigy" campaign compilation reel, 1993 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-166)
  - London--Allen Thomas compilation for J.J. Jordan, 1996 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-167)
  - London--Autumn showreel (NTSC), 2000 (Box U19, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-168)
  - London--Show reel (NTSC), 1998 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-169)
  - London--Nestle Rowntree Kit Kat UK tv and press (NTSC), 1999 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-170)
  - London--Reel for Catie Marshall; Kraft Dairylea Dunkers, Nestle Kit Kat (NTSC), 1999 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-171)
  - London--Shell Tim Davis presentation (NTSC), 2001 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-172)
  - London--Unilever advertising for HPC meeting, 2001 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-173)
  - London--Unilever advertising for HPC meeting, 2001 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-174)
  - Manchester--Creative reel, 1998 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-175)
  - Marion Preston interview, Undated (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-176)
  - Marion Preston retirement, 1995 (Box U20, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-177)
  - Meadowbrook Sterling performances, 1988 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-178)
  - Mexico--5 Star Creative Evening, 1984 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-179)
  - Mexico--Ads compilation (NTSC), 2000 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-180)
  - Mexico--Creative Standards reel, 1997 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-181)
  - Mexico--Ford Creative Regional (JWT Lation America), 2000 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-182)
  - Mumbai (Hindustan Thompson)--2nd Quarter Creative Work, 2000 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-183)
  - Mumbai (Hindustan Thompson)--Godrej Photofridge, Undated (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-184)
  - Muppet Meeting Films--Humorous meeting openings, 1987 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-185)
  - New York Times Best, 1998 (Box U21, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-186)
  - New York Times Best and Worst, 1998 (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-187)
  - JWT North America, 1998 (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-188)
  - Old commercials (Ford), 1983 (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-189)
  - Oscar Mayer Wieners "Marching Song", 1963 (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-190)
  - Paris--Nestle and Liptonic with translations, 1998 (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-191)
  - Paris Rogale--Siemens "Pool", Undated (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-192)
  - Paris Rogale--Siemens "Pool", Undated (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-193)
  - Peru (Lima)--Compilation reel, 1998 (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-194)
  - Peru (Lima)--Commercials of Cusquena, Undated (Box U22, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-195)
  - Polaroid campaign, 1996 (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-196)
  - Portugal--Blue and Green Wave, 1998 (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-197)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--BMW "Hij is af", 1999 (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-198)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Heineken "DJ NY", 1999 (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-199)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Heineken "Shanghai", 1999 (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-200)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--KPN Telecom "Old Friends", 1999 (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-201)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--KPN Telecom "Teddybear", 1999 (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-202)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Nestle Holland Lion "Woman on Couch", Undated (Box U23, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-203)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Radio 3AM "Alternatief", 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-204)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Radio 3AM "Dulfer", 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-205)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Radio 3AM "Nilsson", 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-206)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Radio 3AM "R&B", 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-207)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Radio 3AM "Raggende Mannen", 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-208)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Radio 3AM "Skik", 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-209)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Tolerance Unlimited, 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-210)
  - PPGH/JWT Amsterdam--Zilferen Kruis "Knievel", 1999 (Box U24, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-211)
  - Public Service Worldwide, 1997 (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-212)
  - Quaker Oats 20 spots including "Sheep Dog", Undated (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-213)
  - Ralph Rydholm international advertising reel--Pepsi international, 1984 (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-214)
  - Ralph Rydholm "Stimulus/Response" presentation speakers program part 1, 1984 (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-215)
  - Ralph Rydholm "Stimulus/Response" presentation speakers program part 2, 1984 (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-216)
  - RCA reel 11 spots--Vic Kenyon, Undated (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-217)
  - Red Cross montage, Undated (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-218)
  - Red Cross segment "Boy is Bill Bonds Brutal", Undated (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-219)
  - Reynolds Wrap "Pat and Betty" NFA :32, 1995 (Box U25, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-220)
  - Reel for Chris Jones--International compilation, 1997 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-221)
  - Rome--Tape 00 Technology Presentation, 1995 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-222)
  - Rome--Tape 01 WEG Response, 1995 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-223)
  - Rome--Tape 19 Consultancies Presentations, Brand Group, 1995 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-224)
  - Rome--Tape 20 Product Group, 1995 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-225)
  - Rome--Tape 21 People Group, 1995 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-226)
  - Rome--Tape 22 WEG Response and Discussion, 1995 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-227)
  - Rome--Tape 23 Discussion and Technology Group, 1995 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-228)
  - Sam Meek--Advertising Hall of Fame luncheon, 1986 (Box U26, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-229)
  - San Francisco, Undated (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-230)
  - Sao Paulo--Best of 3rd Quarter, 1998 (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-231)
  - Scott Paper--Purex "Pillow Gang" PAL :30, 1984 (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-232)
  - Segments with new EPT commercial--Entertainment Tonight; Good Morning America; The Home Show, 1992 (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-233)
  - Shanghai--Nike, 1998 (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-234)
  - Shell--Refueling; The Making of Refueling, 1998 (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-235)
  - Sherwin Williams--Comic Abuse; Take on the World; Woodpecker; Dealer's Choice, Undated (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-236)
  - Sydney--Agency TVC "Stitches" PAL, Undated (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-237)
  - Sydney--Kimberly-Clark Kleenex "Pub" :30 NTSC, 2000 (Box U27, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-238)
  - Sydney--Mission Australia brand launch "Lucky Country" :30 NTSC, 2000 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-239)
  - Sydney--Nestle Kit-Kat "Baby Mop" :30 NTSC, 2000 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-240)
  - Sydney--Nestle Kit-Kat "Concrete Garden" :30 NTSC, 2000 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-241)
  - Sydney--Nestle Kit-Kat "Speed Cop" :30 NTSC, 2000 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-242)
  - Sydney--Presentation reel, 1993 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-243)
  - Sydney--Presentation reel, 1993 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-244)
  - Television commercials 35 spots international, 1998 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-245)
  - Television commercials JWT London presentation, 1999 (Box U28, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-246)
  - Thai Airlines Total Branding, 1998 (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-247)
  - Thompson Total Manning, Undated (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-248)
  - Thompson Total Manning, Undated (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-249)
  - Thunderbird announcement spot; 1955 Thunderbird in Design Center Studio (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-250)
  - Tokyo--Creative Standard Review 1st Quarter, 2000 (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-251)
  - Tokyo--Creative Standard Review 2nd Quarter, 2000 (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-252)
  - Tokyo--Creative Standards 1997/1998 (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-253)
  - Toronto--Clorets "Breath Patrol", 1994 (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-254)
  - Toronto--Creative Dept. selected spots, 1995 (Box U29, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-255)
  - Toronto--Creative reel for Mack O'Barr, 1992 (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-256)
  - Toronto--JWT Toronto reel, 1994 (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-257)
  - Toronto--JWT Toronto reel, 1995 (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-258)
  - Toronto--Kellogg various, 1993 (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-259)
  - Toronto--Listerine "Stepping Out", Undated (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-260)
  - Toronto--Northern Telecom "Katie" :30, 1993 (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-261)
  - Toronto--Creative compilation reel, 1996 (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-262)
  - Toronto--Recent creative, 1996 (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-263)
  - Toronto--Spots: 7-Up, Warner-Lambert, Kraft, Undated (Box U30, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-264)
  - Toronto--Various creative: Halls/Philly/K.D. Spaghetti, 1998 (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-265)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-266)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-267)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-268)
  - Vietnam--Various creative, 2000 (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-269)
  - White Castle "Lap It Up", Undated (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-270)
  - Worldwide reel Q2, 2000 (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-271)
  - Worldwide Creative Council London Benchmark Submissions 1-94, 2001 (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-272)
  - Worldwide Creative Council London Benchmark Submissions 95-96, 2001 (Box U31, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-273)
  - Worldwide Executive Group NTSC, 1997 (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-274)
  - Worldwide New Creative, 1998 (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-275)
  - Worldwide Operating Group reel #2, 1994 (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-276)
  - Worldwide Public Service Ads, 1996 (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-277)
  - Worldwide reel 1st quarter 1 of 2, Undated (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-278)
  - Worldwide reel 1st quarter 2 of 2, Undated (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-279)
  - Video Strategies--82V00011 Section 1: Amusements, Leisure and Travel, 1981 (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-280)
  - Video Strategies--82V00012 Appliances and Home Entertainment part 1, 1981 (Box U32, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-281)
  - Video Strategies--82V00013 Appliances and Home Entertainment part 2, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-282)
  - Video Strategies--82V00014 Automotive part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-283)
  - Video Strategies--82V00015 Automotive part 2, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-284)
  - Video Strategies--82V00016 Beverages part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-285)
  - Video Strategies--82V00017 Beverages part 2, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-286)
  - Video Strategies--82V00018 Cosmetics and Personal Hygiene part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-287)
  - Video Strategies--82V00020 financial and Business Strategies, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-288)
  - Video Strategies--82V00021 Food part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-289)
  - Video Strategies--82V00022 Food part 2, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-290)
  - Video Strategies--82V00023 Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-291)
  - Video Strategies--82V00024 Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food part 2, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-292)
  - Video Strategies--82V00025 Laundry and Paper Products part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-293)
  - Video Strategies--82V00026 Laundry and Paper Products part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-294)
  - Video Strategies--82V00027 Medicines, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-295)
  - Video Strategies--82V00028 Retail and Apparel part 1, 1981 (Box U33, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-296)
  - Video Strategies--82V00029 Retail and Apparel part 2, 1981 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-297)
  - Video Strategies--82V00030 Toys and Games, 1981 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-298)
  - Video Strategies--83V00027 Amusements, Leisure and Travel part 1, 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-299)
  - Video Strategies--83V00028 Amusements, Leisure and Travel part 2, 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-300)
  - Video Strategies--83V00029 Sections 2-3 (Appliances and home entertainment, Automotive), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-301)
  - Video Strategies--83V00030 Sections 4-5 (Beverages, Cosmetics and Personal Hygiene), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-302)
  - Video Strategies--83V00031 Financial and Business Services, 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-303)
  - Video Strategies--83V00032 Sections 7 and 12 (Food, Toys and Games), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-304)
  - Video Strategies--83V00033 Sections 8-9 (Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food; Laundry and Paper Products), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-305)
  - Video Strategies--83V00034 Sections; 10-11 (Medicines, Retail and Apparel), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-306)
  - Video Strategies--83V00036 Amusements, Leisure and Travel part 1, 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-307)
  - Video Strategies--83V00037 Sections 2-3 (Appliances and home entertainment, Automotive), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-308)
  - Video Strategies--83V00038 Sections 4,5,8 (Beverages; Cosmetics and Personal Hygiene; Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-309)
  - Video Strategies--83V00039 Section 6,9 (Laundry and Paper Products; Financial and Business Services), 1983 (Box U34, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-310)
  - Video Strategies--83V00040 Sections 7,10 (Food; Medicines), 1983 (Box U35, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-311)
  - Video Strategies--83V00041 Sections 11,12 (Retail and Apparel; Toys and Games), 1983 (Box U35, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-312)
  - 50s TV Classics: Burns and Allen Show "Car Accident", 1987 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-001)
  - 50s TV Classics: Burns and Allen Show "Checking Account", 1987 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-002)
  - 50s TV Classics: Burns and Allen Show "Nieces Visit", 1987 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-003)
  - 50s TV Classics: Groucho Marx, 1987 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-004)
  - 50s TV Classics: "You Bet Your Life starring Groucho Marx", 1987 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-005)
  - AAAA: Fifty Years of Free TV, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-006)
  - Ad Industry: Self-Regulation 24:00, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-007)
  - Ad Industry: Self-Regulation 24:00, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-008)
  - Ad Industry: Self-Regulation 24:00, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-009)
  - Addams Family, 1964 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-010)
  - Advertising Educational Foundation--Ad Council: Finding Solutions 23:25, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-011)
  - Advertising Educational Foundation--Ad Industry: Self-Regulation 24:15, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-012)
  - Advertising Educational Foundation--Behind the Scenes 29:12, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-013)
  - Advertising Educational Foundation--Goodbye Guesswork: Research 27:01, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-014)
  - AICP Show: The Art and Technique of the American Television Commercial, 2000 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-015)
  - Archives 3 Segments, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-016)
  - Association of Italian Handicapped; Chilean Red Cross. PAL, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-017)
  - AVC 1" Transfer reel 11/6/97, 1997 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-018)
  - AVC 1" Transfer reel 12/4/97, 1997 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-019)
  - AVC 1" Transfer reel 1/8/98, 1998 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-020)
  - AVC 1" Transfer reel 3/5/98, 1998 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-021)
  - AVC 1" Transfer reel 5/7/98, 1998 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-022)
  - AVC 1" Transfer reel 8/6/98, 1998 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-023)
  - Behind the Scenes: The Advertising Process at Work (AEF), 1990 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-024)
  - Behind the Scenes (Campaign development) 29:00, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-025)
  - Behind the Scenes (Campaign development) 29:00, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-026)
  - The Big Picture no. 1, 1994 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-027)
  - The Big Picture no. 1, 1994 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-028)
  - The Brain Game (JWT sponsored on English Channel 4), 1992 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-029)
  - Builders Square/American Express direct mail video, 1995 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-030)
  - Bye Bye Babushka, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-031)
  - Chicago--1994 Minda Lansang Media Directors Conference, Udaipur India, "The New Moghuls" (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-032)
  - Chris Jones Chicago remarks, 1998 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-033)
  - Clio Awards reel 1, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-034)
  - Clio Awards reel 2, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-035)
  - Cole's Quality Foods 50th anniversary video, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-036)
  - Commodore Awards "Big Picture" issue 3, 1995 (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-037)
  - Compilation reel 10 spots, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-038)
  - Compilation reel 10 spots, Undated (Box V1, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-039)
  - Creative Library Transfer Reel, 1996 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-040)
  - D and AD (Direction and Art Direction?) Showreel, 2000 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-041)
  - DeBeers/Bally reel, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-042)
  - Detroit--1996 Adcraft reel (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-043)
  - Detroit--1996 Adcraft reel (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-044)
  - Detroit--1996 Outdoor presentation (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-045)
  - Detroit--1996 Outdoor presentation (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-046)
  - Detroit--2 Minute Ford Millennium, 1999 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-047)
  - Detroit--A+ Creative Award/A+ Advertiser Award winners and finalists AAAA 75:00, 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-048)
  - Detroit--A+ Creative Award/A+ Advertiser Award winners and finalists AAAA 75:00, 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-049)
  - Detroit--Allen Thomas Adcrafter presentation, 1992 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-050)
  - Detroit--American Express: The Essence of the Brand 7:38, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-051)
  - Detroit--The Big Picture issue #1, 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-052)
  - Detroit--Cannes winners part 2, 1993 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-053)
  - Detroit--Cannes Worldwide Creative Commercials, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-054)